Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education In Asia Records, Addendum A
Yale University Divinity School Library
- College Files -- Addendum, Series IV
  - Republic of China (Taiwan)
    - Tunghai University
      - Chen, Chien-sen, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 1040)
      - Chen. Ching-ho, 1956-1957 (Box 79, Folder 1040)
      - Chen, Hsien-fang, 1958-1971 (Box 79, Folder 1041)
      - Chen, Johnson T. F., 1955-1971 (Box 79, Folder 1042)
      - Chen, Paul T. R., 1955 (Box 79, Folder 1042)
      - Chen, Shih-haueh, 1962 Dec-1968 (Box 79, Folder 1043-1044)
      - Chen, Theodore R. E., 1954 Apr-Sep (Box 79, Folder 1045-1047)
      - Chen, Yu-chung, 1962 Dec 1966 Mar (Box 79, Folder 1048)
      - Chen, Yu-chung, 1966 Apr-1971 (Box 80, Folder 1049-1051)
      - Cheng, Chen yu, 1956 Jul, 1957 Jan (Box 80, Folder 1052)
      - Cheng, Teh an (Andrew), 1958 Jul 1969 Mar (Box 80, Folder 1053-1055)
      - Cheng, Tien-fang, 1952-1954 (Box 80, Folder 1056)
      - Chinese Civilization, Institute in -Chinese Culture, 1961-1962, 1965-1970 (Box 80, Folder 1057)
      - Choir - Choral, 1967-1970 (Box 80, Folder 1058)
      - Chou, I kwei, 1966-1970 (Box 80, Folder 1059-1061)
      - Chow, Lien hwa - Christian Literature Center, 1960-1964 (Box 80, Folder 1062)
      - Christian Church - Chronological record, 1958,1962,1966,1970 (Box 80, Folder 1063)
      - Chuang Che, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 1064)
      - Cochran, Anne, 1953-1954 Aug (Box 80, Folder 1065)
      - Cochran, Anne, 1954 Oct 1964 Jun (Box 81, Folder 1066-1069)
      - Cochran, Anne--Textbook project, 1964-1967 (Box 81, Folder 1070)
      - Commencement, 1965-1967, 1969-1971 (Box 81, Folder 1071)
      - Committee minutes, misc., 1953-1957 (Box 81, Folder 1072)
      - Conference of Christian University Presidents, 1956 (Box 81, Folder 1073)
      - Conservation program, 1966 Jan, 1969-1971 (Box 81, Folder 1074)
      - Constitution and By-laws, 1959,1970,n.d. (Box 81, Folder 1075)
      - Controller, 1963-1964 Jun (Box 81, Folder 1076-1077)
      - Crawford, Louise, 1958-1971 (Box 81, Folder 1078-1081)
      - Curriculum, 1955-57, 1959-60 (Box 82, Folder 1082)
      - Curriculum committee, 1955-1956 (Box 82, Folder 1082)
      - D general (Box 82, Folder 1083)
      - Dialogue (International Essay Contest), 1962 May (Box 82, Folder 1084)
      - Directors, Board of--General, 1953-1957,1970 (Box 82, Folder 1085)
      - Directors, Board of--Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 82, Folder 1086)
      - Directors. Board of--Minutes, 1960-1971 (Box 82, Folder 1087-1088)
      - E general (incl. Exchange students) (Box 82, Folder 1089)
      - Educational objectives, 1956-1957 (Box 82, Folder 1090)
      - Engineering College, Chemical Engineering Dept., 1956-1969 (Box 82, Folder 1091)
      - Engineering College, Industrial Engineering Dept., 1962-1967 (Box 82, Folder 1092)
      - Engineering College, Lab equipment, 1964-1969 (Box 82, Folder 1093)
      - Engineering College Quadrangle, 1965-1970 (Box 82, Folder 1094)
      - Engineering College Quadrangle, Blueprints, 1966 (Box 82, Folder 1095)
      - English courses - English teaching research project, 1953-1959 (Box 82, Folder 1096)
      - Evaluation and Planning, 1962-1971 (Box 82, Folder 1097)
      - Exchange professors, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 1097)
      - Expenditures, 1952-1956 (Box 82, Folder 1098)
      - Extension and Development Comeittees, 1955-1959 (Box 82, Folder 1099)
      - F general (Box 83, Folder 1100-1101)
      - Faculty and staff, 1955-1971 (Box 83, Folder 1102-1103)
      - Faculty and ataff lists, 1962-1971 (Box 83, Folder 1104)
      - Faculty and staff retirement plans, 1958-1970 (Box 83, Folder 1105)
      - Faculty openings, 1954-1971 (Box 83, Folder 1106-1107)
      - Faculty salaries, 1955-1971 (Box 83, Folder 1108-1109)
      - Faculty Settling-in Allowance, 1968-1970 (Box 83, Folder 1110)
      - Faculty Welfare Fund, 1961-1962 (Box 83, Folder 1110)
      - Fan, Hung-chih, 1965-1967 (Box 83, Folder 1111)
      - Faucett. Lawrence V., 1962 (Box 83, Folder 1111)
      - Fellowships (United Board), 1960-1971 (Box 83, Folder 1112)
      - Financial reports, 1955-1964 (Box 83, Folder 1113-1115)
      - Financial reports, 1965-1971 (Box 84, Folder 1116-1118)
      - Fire insurance, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 1119)
      - Foreign Language Department, 1958 (Box 84, Folder 1119)
      - Founding, 1952-1958 (Box 84, Folder 1120)
      - Fryling, Charles F., 1965-1966 (Box 84, Folder 1121)
      - Fund raising, 1969 (Box 84, Folder 1121)
      - G general (Box 84, Folder 1122)
      - Governors, Board of, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 1123)
      - Graduates, 1959,1961,1968 (Box 84, Folder 1124)
      - Graham, Thomas B., 1953-1960 Feb (Box 84, Folder 1125-1127)
      - Groundbreaking, 1953 Nov (Box 84, Folder 1128)
      - H general (Box 84, Folder 1129-1130)
      - Hagman, Robert B., 1955 Nov 1956 Feb (Box 84, Folder 1131)
      - Han, Lih-wu, 1952-1958 (Box 84, Folder 1132-1133)
      - Han, Pao teh, 1966 Dec-1970 (Box 85, Folder 1134-1135)
      - Hanson, Anders B., 1956-1959 (Box 85, Folder 1136)
      - Harvard-Yenching Research Grants, 1966-1971 (Box 85, Folder 1137-1138)
      - Ho, Hoh-shou, 1968 Nov-1970 Apr (Box 85, Folder 1139)
      - Housing, 1957-1960 (Box 85, Folder 1139)
      - Hsieh, Mao-chang, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 1139)
      - Hsieh, Van-chen, 1967-1970 (Box 85, Folder 1140)
      - Hu, Chia-yean, 1970 Jan (Box 85, Folder 1141)
      - Hua, Chang-i, 1962 Dec-1963 Mar (Box 85, Folder 1142)
      - Huang, Li Lieng, 1955 Aug (Box 85, Folder 1142)
      - Huenemann, Ralph, 1961-1974 Jan (Box 85, Folder 1143)
      - I general (Box 85, Folder 1144)
      - J general (Box 85, Folder 1145)
      - Jackson, H. N., 1956 (Box 85, Folder 1146)
      - Jen, Fung-chung, 1957 (Box 85, Folder 1146)
      - Jockheck, Carl F., 1963 Oct-1967 Jun (Box 85, Folder 1147-1151)
      - Jockheck, Carl F., 1967 Jul- 1970 (Box 86, Folder 1152-1158)
      - Jockheck, Lillian, 1964 Aug-1970 Jan (Box 86, Folder 1159)
      - Re: Tunghai Journal, 1958-1962, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 1160)
      - Juntin, William F. and Margaret, 1969-1971 (Box 86, Folder 1161-1162)
      - K general (Box 86, Folder 1163)
      - Kao, Chao-jen (Julian), 1961-1971 (Box 86, Folder 1164)
      - Kao, Chen-hua, 1962-1969 (Box 86, Folder 1165)
      - Kao, S. C., 1967-1968 (Box 87, Folder 1166)
      - King, John Reed, 1969-1971 (Box 87, Folder 1166)
      - Kirk, Florence A., 1958 Dec- 1970 (Box 87, Folder 1167-1170)
      - Krull, Lenice, 1955-1956 (Box 87, Folder 1171)
      - Ku, Tun-jou and I-ching, 1959-1969 (Box 87, Folder 1171)
      - Kuo, Albert Tung-Yao, 1964-1973 (Box 87, Folder 1172-1173)
      - Kuo, Wen-tung, 1967-1971 (Box 87, Folder 1174)
      - Kuo, Yung-chu, 1964-1968 (Box 87, Folder 1175)
      - L general (La-Li) (Box 87, Folder 1176)
      - L general (Lia-Ly) (Box 88, Folder 1177)
      - Labor problem, 1956-1970 (Box 88, Folder 1178)
      - Land case (incl. map), 1966-1971 (Box 88, Folder 1179)
      - Language teaching, 1959-1967 (Box 88, Folder 1180)
      - Lee, Yu-ming (Lincoln C. S.), 1961-1964 (Box 88, Folder 1190)
      - Lewis, Paul, 1965-1967 (Box 88, Folder 1191)
      - Li, Loretta Ho, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 1192)
      - Liang, Run Fu, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 1192)
      - Library, 1956-1960, 1963-1971 (Box 88, Folder 1193-1195)
      - Library Science Program, 1957-1971 (Box 88, Folder 1196)
      - Library surveys, 1963, 1966 (Box 88, Folder 1197)
      - Life Science Reaearch Center, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 1198)
      - Lighte, Peter, 1970-1971 (Box 88, Folder 1196)
      - Lin general (Box 88, Folder 1199)
      - Lin, David Chien-Yeh, 1962-1966 (Box 89, Folder 1200)
      - Lin, Shu-ming, 1954-1956 (Box 89, Folder 1201)
      - Lin, Wen-chan, 1964-1966 Feb (Box 89, Folder 1202-1204)
      - Lin, Yu-keng, 1952-1955 (Box 89, Folder 1205)
      - Literature program, 1956 (Box 89, Folder 1205)
      - Liu, Jung chao and Marlita, 1955-1960 (Box 89, Folder 1206-1209)
      - Liu, Shu hsien, 1963 Jan, 1964 Jan-Feb (Box 89, Folder 1210)
      - Lo, Janet Pi, 1965-1968 (Box 89, Folder 1211-1213)
      - Lovejoy, Allen P. and Jean, 1959-1963 May (Box 90, Folder 1214-1226)
      - Lovejoy, Jean, 1961 Jun-1963 May (Box 90, Folder 1227)
      - Lu, Kun-hai, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 1228)
      - Luce, H. V., 100th Anniversary of Birth, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1229)
      - Luce Chapel, 1953 Dec-1971 Apr (Box 91, Folder 1230-1237)
      - Luce Chapel--Blueprints (Box 91, Folder 1238-1239)
      - Luce Chapel--Dedication, 1963 (Box 91, Folder 1240)
      - Luce Chapel--Drawings in relation to campus, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 1241)
      - Luce Chapel--Early plans and photos (Box 91, Folder 1242-1243)
      - Luce Chapel--Publicity, 1958 (Box 91, Folder 1244)
      - M general (Box 92, Folder 1245-1246)
      - MacInnis, Donald, 1955-1956 (Box 92, Folder 1247)
      - MacMillan, Hugh, 1956-1962 (Box 92, Folder 1248)
      - Maier, Barney and Eleanor, 1969-1971 (Box 92, Folder 1249)
      - Maintenance Funds, 1962-1966 (Box 92, Folder 1250)
      - Map, n.d. (Box 92, Folder 1251)
      - Mei, Y. P., 1964-1970 (Box 92, Folder 1252)
      - Middle School, 1962-1970 (Box 92, Folder 1253)
      - Ministry of Education (C. L. Huang), 1961 (Box 92, Folder 1254)
      - Miscellaneous, 1952-1967 (Box 92, Folder 1255-1261)
      - Music Department, 1964-1971 (Box 92, Folder 1262)
      - N general (Box 92, Folder 1263)
      - Nee, Ling-sung (Timothy), 1968-1969 (Box 93, Folder 1264)
      - Newsletter, 1968-1971 (Box 93, Folder 1265-1267)
      - Oberlin-Shansi, 1967-1971 (Box 93, Folder 1268)
      - Opening, 1955 (Box 93, Folder 1269)
      - Orientation advice, 1958-1968 (Box 93, Folder 1270)
      - P general (Box 93, Folder 1271)
      - Photo contest, 1962-1963 (Box 93, Folder 1272)
      - Photographs, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 1272)
      - Pi, Janet (Che-yen), 1963-1965 Jan (Box 93, Folder 1272-1273)
      - Pierce Memorial Hospital Fund, 1957-1958 (Box 93, Folder 1274)
      - Pilot Community, 1970-1971 (Box 93, Folder 1275)
      - Polson, Robert, 1955 Nov-1956 (Box 93, Folder 1276)
      - Preparatory committee, 1952 Jun-1953 (Box 93, Folder 1276)
      - President's Reports, 1953-1964 (Box 93, Folder 1277-1278)
      - President's Reports, 1965-1968 (Box 94, Folder 1279)
      - Priest, Elsie N., 1955-1957 May (Box 94, Folder 1280-1294)
      - Priest, Elsie N., 1957 Jun-1959 Mar (Box 95, Folder 1295-1310)
      - Priest, Elsie N., 1959 Apr-1960 (Box 96, Folder 1311-1320)
      - Publications, lists of, 1964-1966 (Box 96, Folder 1321)
      - Publicity, 1955, 1965, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 1322)
      - R general (Box 96, Folder 1323)
      - Reports: Princeton-in-Asia, 1957-1963 (Box 96, Folder 1324)
      - Reports: Professional chairs, 1955 (Box 96, Folder 1325)
      - Reports: Miscellaneous, 1956-1958, 1968,1970 (Box 96, Folder 1326)
      - Reports: Progress, 1954-1955 (Box 96, Folder 1327)
      - Representatives, 1962-1963 (Box 97, Folder 1328)
      - Research, 1965-1967 (Box 97, Folder 1329)
      - Rural Community Survey, 1959-1970 (Box 97, Folder 1330)
      - Rose, Juanelva, 1964-1971 (Box 97, Folder 1331)
      - S general, 1955-1964 (Box 97, Folder 1332-1333)
      - Scholarships, 1955-1971 (Box 97, Folder 1334-1336)
      - Scholarships--Architecture - Scott, Ewing C. Memorial, 1960-1966 (Box 97, Folder 1337)
      - Science College, 1968-1971 (Box 97, Folder 1338)
      - Schroeder, Carl J., 1964-1968 (Box 97, Folder 1338)
      - Seng, Harris B. H., 1956-1971 (Box 97, Folder 1339)
      - Severinghaus, Sheldon R., 1964-1969 (Box 97, Folder 1340-1342)
      - Shadick - Shepherd, 1956-1969 (Box 97, Folder 1343)
      - Shing, Johnson, 1956-1957 (Box 97, Folder 1344)
      - Shutt. Charles N., 1954-1958 (Box 97, Folder 1345-1346)
      - Smith, Richard, 1968-1970 (Box 98, Folder 1347)
      - Soochow Alumni Fund, 1954 (Box 98, Folder 1348)
      - Sovik, Arne, 1954-1955 (Box 98, Folder 1349)
      - Speidel, William and Elena, 1958, 1964-1967, 1970-1971 (Box 98, Folder 1350)
      - Squatters, 1963-1971 (Box 98, Folder 1351)
      - Statistics, 1955-1971 (Box 98, Folder 1352-1353)
      - Stoves, refrigerators, etc., 1965-1970 (Box 98, Folder 1354)
      - Students, Activities and Conditions, 1958-1970 (Box 98, Folder 1355)
      - Students, Costs, 1963-1970 (Box 98, Folder 1356)
      - Students, Labor, 1957-1965 (Box 98, Folder 1357)
      - Studies and Surveys, 1970-1971 (Box 98, Folder 1358)
      - Su, Edgar C. H., 1955-1957 (Box 98, Folder 1359)
      - Sun, Ching-shan, 1969-1971 (Box 98, Folder 1360)
      - Sun, Shang-lieng, 1963-1965 (Box 98, Folder 1361-1363)
      - Sun, Wesley K. C., 1961-1971 (Box 98, Folder 1364)
      - Sun, Yung-lin, 1961 (Box 98, Folder 1365)
      - Sung, Abraham L. H., 1956 (Box 98, Folder 1365)
      - Survey: Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 98, Folder 1366)
      - Survey: Report, 1964 Feb-Mar (Box 98, Folder 1367)
      - T general, 1952-1960 (Box 98, Folder 1368-1369)
      - Taiwan-Hong Kong committee, 1953-1958 (Box 98, Folder 1370)
      - Tadio, Felix, 1964 (Box 99, Folder 1371)
      - Tainan Theological College, 1954-1959 (Box 99, Folder 1371)
      - "Taiwan's Land Reform " - Tang, S. C., 1956,1962-1968 (Box 99, Folder 1372)
      - Tang, Shou-chien, 1955-1957 (Box 99, Folder 1373-1374)
      - Tenth Anniversary, 1964 (Box 99, Folder 1375)
      - Thelin, Mark and Virginia, 1961-1971 Jul (Box 99, Folder 1376-1377)
      - Third College (Industrial Engineering, 1961-1963 (Box 99, Folder 1378)
      - Thomforde, Christopher, 1969-1971 (Box 99, Folder 1379)
      - Translation project, 1959-1968 (Box 99, Folder 1380)
      - Tosi, Chi-ching, 1969-1971 (Box 99, Folder 1381)
      - Tasi Paul C., 1957 (Box 99, Folder 1382)
      - Tsai, Pei-huo, 1954-1957 (Box 99, Folder 1383)
      - Tsai, Stephen, 1954-1957 (Box 99, Folder 1384-1387)
      - Tsai, Stephen, 1958-1971 Feb (Box 100, Folder 1388-1389)
      - Tseng, Beauson, 1955-1957 Aug (Box 100, Folder 1390-1399)
      - Tseng, P, 1964-1968 (Box 101, Folder 1400)
      - Tsu, Wen-Kwei (John Gabriel), 1955 (Box 101, Folder 1401)
      - Tu, Heng-tse, 1968-1970 (Box 101, Folder 1402-1403)
      - Tung, Ta-cheng, 1956 (Box 101, Folder 1404)
      - U general (Box 101, Folder 1405)
      - United Board, Committee on Tunghai, 1953-1955 (Box 101, Folder 1406)
      - United Board, "Memorandum to the ...", 1952 (Box 101, Folder 1407)
      - United Board Tour, 1969 (Box 101, Folder 1408)
      - University Cabinet Meetings, minutes, 1956, 1960-1971 (Box 101, Folder 1409-1413)
      - University Council, 1956, 1961, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 1414)
      - Urban Housing, 1970
      - V general (Box 101, Folder 1415)
      - Vickers, Elizabeth M., 1969 (Box 101, Folder 1416)
      - Visiting Professorship, 1963-1965 (Box 101, Folder 1417)
      - Visitor's impressions, 1963-1968 (Box 101, Folder 1418)
      - W general (Box 102, Folder 1419)
      - Wang, C. - Y. (general) (Box 102, Folder 1420)
      - Wang, Gene T., 1968-1971 (Box 102, Folder 1421)
      - Wang, Lucy, 1962-1967 (Box 102, Folder 1422-1425)
      - Water system, 1963,1965-1971 (Box 102, Folder 1426)
      - Western Languages and Literature, Dept. of, 1966-1971 (Box 102, Folder 1427)
      - Wiant, Paul P., 1953-1955 (Box 102, Folder 1428)
      - Wong, C. - V., 1955-1957 (Box 102, Folder 1429)
      - World Day of Prayer, 1964-1967 (Box 102, Folder 1429)
      - Wu, Ching-mu, 1967-1971 (Box 102, Folder 1430)
      - Wu, Teh-yao--Biographical data, 1962-1970 (Box 102, Folder 1431)
      - Wu, Teh-yao, 1954-1960 Jun (Box 103, Folder 1432-1447)
      - Wu, Teh-yao, 1960 Jul-1971 Aug (Box 104, Folder 1448-1463)
      - Y general (Box 105, Folder 1464)
      - Yang, Chia-chi, 1966-1971 Jun (Box 105, Folder 1465-1466)
      - Yang, Ching-an, 1956-1958 (Box 105, Folder 1467)
      - Yang, Shu-chia, 1956, 1957, 1962 (Box 105, Folder 1467)
      - Young, Herrick B., 1969 Sep-1972 Jan (Box 105, Folder 1468-1477)
      - Yu, Ming-jenn, 1969-1970 (Box 105, Folder 1478)
      - The Asian Environmental Review, 1977 (Box 108, Folder 1494)
      - Yearbook, 1959, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 1498)
      - Tunghai News, 1960-1961 (Box 108, Folder 1499)
      - Tunghai Journal, 1978, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 1500)
      - East Wind, 1958-1971 (Box 109, Folder 1501)
      - Bulletin of the Graduate Institute of History, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 1502)
      - Tunghai Student, 1969 (Box 109, Folder 1503)
      - Alumni Bulletin, 1969-1977 (Box 109, Folder 1504)
      - Pamphlets, 1956-1969 (Box 109, Folder 1505)
      - Pamphlets, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1506)
      - Articles, 1955-1965, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1507)
- Audio-Visual Materials -- Addendum, Series V
  The materials in this Series are organized by format:
  Photographs
  Slides
  Sound Recordings
  Within these categories, the materials are organized by institution. Audiovisual materials regarding some of these institutions are also available in Manuscript Group No. 11, Series V.
  - Photographs
    - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia
      - Mat print portraits of William Fenn, Unidentified man (Box 250, Folder 3510)
    - Yonsei University, 1956
      - Buildings and Scenes, 1904-1972, n.d.
      - Postcards - Buildings and Scenes
      - War Damages, n.d.
      - Reception, 1932
      - Commencement, 1972
      - Faculty, 1972, n.d.
      - Student Life, 1955-1972
    - Philippine Christian College
      - Miscellaneous, c.1950
    - Silliman Universitv
      - Portraits, n.d.
      - Scenes from Campus Life, n.d.
      - Health Care, n.d.
      - Buildings and Scenes
      - Conferences and Special Events
      - Community Development, n.d.
      - Teaching, n.d.
      - Agriculture, n.d.
      - Weaving, n.d.
      - Insignia, n.d. (Box 250, Folder 3513)
      - Negatives, n.d.
    - Chung Chi College
      - Miscellaneous, 1951-1964, n.d. (Box 251, Folder 3514)
    - Tunghai University
      - Miscellaneous (Box 251, Folder 3515)
    - Princeton-in-Asia, 1955-1961, n.d.
      - Photograph Album, n.d. (Box 285, Folder 3963)
  - Slides
    - Yonsei University, n.d. (Box 252, Folder 3516)
    - Silliman University, n.d. (Box 252, Folder 3517)
    - Tunghai University, n.d. (Box 252, Folder 3518)
  - Sound Recordings
    - Tunghai University, n.d. (Box 253, Folder 3519)
- Related Organizations and Publications--Addendum, Series VI
  Series VI is divided into the following categories:
  1) Related Organizations
  2) Princeton-in-Asia records
  3) Related Publications
  a) Concerning Education
  b) Conference Publications
  The organizations are listed alphabetically, with descriptive subheadings added as warranted by the amount of material available for an organization. The publications are listed chronologically within the established categories.
  - Related Organizations
    - All-India Association for Christian Higher Education: Newsletter, 1971-1980 (Box 254, Folder 3520-3523)
    - Asia Christian Colleges Association: Bulletin, 1952-1971 (Box 255, Folder 3524-3526)
    - Asia Christian Colleges Association: Pamphlets, n.d. (Box 255, Folder 3527)
    - Association of Christian Universities and Colleges in Asla: "ACUCA Exchange", 1977-1979 (Box 255, Folder 3528)
    - ACUCA: Five-Year Development Plan, 1979-1983 (Box 255, Folder 3528)
    - China Medical Board: Annual Reports, 1958-1967 (Box 255, Folder 3529)
    - Council on Christian Higher Education in Asia (COCHEA): Background Material to Formation Of Organization, 1952-1955, n.d. (Box 256, Folder 3530)
    - COCHEA: Correspondence, 1953-1960 (Box 256, Folder 3531-3533)
    - COCHEA: Membership, 1954-1959 (Box 256, Folder 3534)
    - COCHEA: Minutes, 1953-1960 (Box 256, Folder 3535-3540)
    - COCHEA:"Asia Colleges Newsletter", 1955-1958 (Box 256, Folder 3541)
    - COCHEA: Newsletter: Related Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 256, Folder 3542)
    - COCHEA: Papers and Reports, 1955-1958 (Box 256, Folder 3543)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: General, 1950-1968, n.d. (Box 257, Folder 3544)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: Ahmednagar College, 1957-1959 (Box 257, Folder 3545)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: Bantura Christian College, 1958-1959 (Box 257, Folder 3545)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: Christ Church College, Kanpur, 1958-1959 (Box 257, Folder 3545)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: Christian Medical College-Punjab, 1952-1960 (Box 257, Folder 3546)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: Elizabeth Voorhees College, 1953 (Box 257, Folder 3547)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: Isabella Thoburn College, 1953-1957, n.d. (Box 257, Folder 3548)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: Lady Doak College, 1958. n.d. (Box 257, Folder 3549)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: Mar Thoma College, 1956-1958 (Box 257, Folder 3550)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: St. Andrew's College, 1958-1959 (Box 257, Folder 3551)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: St. Christopher's Training College, 1947, 1952-1959 (Box 257, Folder 3552)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: St. Columba's College, 1957-1959 (Box 257, Folder 3553)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: St. John's College, 1952-1958 (Box 257, Folder 3553)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: St. Paul's Cathedral Mission College, 1956-1959 (Box 257, Folder 3553)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: Sarah Tucker College, 1956-1959 (Box 257, Folder 3554)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: Serampore College, 1953-1965, n.d. (Box 257, Folder 3555)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: Union Christian Training College, 1956-1957 (Box 257, Folder 3556)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: Vellore Christian Medical College, 1959, n.d. (Box 257, Folder 3557)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: Vellore: Newsletter, 1952-1960 (Box 257, Folder 3558)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: Vellore: Pamphlets, 1951-1964 (Box 257, Folder 3559)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: Wilson College, 1957-1958, n.d. (Box 258, Folder 3560)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: Women's Christian College-Madras, 1953-1959 (Box 258, Folder 3561)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--India: Women's C. C.: Pamphlets, 1952-1961 (Box 258, Folder 3562)
    - COCHEA: Colleges-Indonesia :General, 1956, 1958 (Box 258, Folder 3563)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--Japan: National Christian Education Asso., 1953-1957, n.d. (Box 258, Folder 3564)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--Japan: Aoyama Gakuin, 1957 (Box 258, Folder 3565)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--Japan: Central Theological College, 1953, n.d. (Box 258, Folder 3565)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--Japan: Doshisha, 1951-1954, n.d. (Box 258, Folder 3565)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--Japan: International Christian University, 1953-1958 (Box 258, Folder 3566-3575)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--Japan: International Christian University, 1958-1959, n.d. (Box 259, Folder 3576-3577)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--Japan: International C. U.: Pamphlets, 1953-1961, n.d. (Box 259, Folder 3578)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--Japan: Kwansei Gakuin, 1949 (Box 259, Folder 3579)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--Japan: Meiji Gakuin, 1956, n.d. (Box 259, Folder 3579)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--Japan: St. Paul's University, 1949, 1955, n.d. (Box 259, Folder 3580)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--Japan: Seiwa Junior College, 1957 (Box 259, Folder 3580)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--Japan: Shitoku Christian College, 1953 (Box 259, Folder 3580)
    - COCHEA: Colleges--Japan: Tokyo Woman's Christian College, 1952-1962, n.d. (Box 259, Folder 3581)
    - COCHEA: Colleges-Korea :Chosun Christian University, n.d. (Box 259, Folder 3582)
    - COCHEA: Colleges-Korea: Keimyung College, 1955 (Box 259, Folder 3582)
    - COCHEA: Colleges-Korea: Presbyterian Theological Seminary, n.d. (Box 259, Folder 3582)
    - COCHEA: Colleges-Korea: Seoul National University, 1957 (Box 259, Folder 3582)
    - COCHEA: Colleges-Korea: Union Christian College, 1958, n.d. (Box 259, Folder 3583)
    - COCHEA: Colleges-Korea: Yonsei University, 1957, n.d. (Box 259, Folder 3583)
    - COCHEA: Colleges-Pakistan: Kinnaird College for Women, 1951-1955 (Box 259, Folder 3584)